Your last junior high sports festival is just 19 days, 18 hours, and 23 minutes away.
So exact.
Like you didn't do the same for Valentine's Day.
Last year, my precious blue team suffered a horrible and tragic defeat and embarrassingly came in third.
This year we will win with teamwork, cooperation, and ardent determination.
This is something I want to hold over.
All the other teachers smirking heads!
Don't say that part out loud!
Come on, give me a break.
And just like that, the most pointless event of every school year was once again fast approaching.
Could we just not?
Hey.
Huh?
So how about it?
You up for it?
You want to be our knight?
You're what?
Okay.
So
One thing I want to do is play a little help.
You're what?
I'm sorry I want to talk about that out loud.
For our mock cavalry battle.
Why me?
I mean, you're kinda puny.
But look like you got...
He's not puny!
I was gonna say you look like you got guts, but guess not.
He does, though!
You've said enough already!
Yeah? You turn him down?
Yeah.
I'm joining in.
Although, in my opinion, I think they should mix up the girls and boys.
And we wear bathing suits, and instead of stealing hats, we'd steal bikini tops and...
Even perfect TV shows don't do that.
But you know...
Huh?
What do you want?
Nah, nothing really.
I just noticed you've shot up a lot.
Growing in like a forest down there yet?
Why do we have to talk about this?
Last year's fest. You got hurt during it, right?
What?
You know, during the centipede race with Yamada.
Oh, yeah.
Sorry about that time.
You know, for telling people you pulled her down and stuff.
That was my bad.
Already forgot about it.
Although, she did set things straight.
He didn't!
I think he just tried to instead keep me from getting hurt.
In fact, that's when I first realized Yamada was pretty cool, you know?
I...
Where'd you go?!
Now that I think about it, that might have been the first time we ever interacted.
Here we go!
Ready?
One, two!
Why is Ana Yamada here?
And in a competition for everyone who wasn't picked for the others?
Said she was a model or something, huh?
Bet she joined on purpose so she could look even better surrounded by trash like us.
Kill me now!
Here we go! Ready? One, two! One, two!
Why is Anayamada here, and in a competition for everyone who wasn't picked for the others?
Said she was a model or something, huh? Bet she joined on purpose so she could look even better surrounded by trash like us.
Kill me now!
Ichikawa!
I was just thinking about last year's sports festival.
Are you okay?
This sucks!
Oh, you still have a bit of a scar.
Sorry.
And thanks.
Arichi?
Huh?
What's up?
Kansuki.
Hey, on your white day date, you were with Yamada and Ichikawa, right?
I told you not to tell him about me seeing them!
Sorry!
Um, hey!
Ichikawa!
Join the cavalry!
Huh?
Let's go one-on-one!
Geez!
You can at least react!
Not that I really care!
I mean, if you don't wanna-
I-
Uh...
Fine, I'll do it for you!
Yeah, for me, huh?
It doesn't really matter who wins or loses.
Jeez, you can at least react not that I really care. I mean if you don't
Fine, I'll do it for you
Yeah for me, huh?
It doesn't really matter who wins or loses
But for some reason, I really don't want to lose
Can't lose. Shoot, that wasn't the right pace
People say working out too much while you're growing can make you short. Yeah, guess I ought to call it a day
Now that doesn't make sense almost all of the tallest athletes have been playing since they were kids. Have they not?
I uh, well, I mean
Go ahead and look it up. No, thanks. I don't want the algorithm thinking I'm a gym rat and get lost can't get caught talking to myself
See there are dogs around it
I
You need something cold as ice I
Was having a little chat with one taro why not use real words then he wouldn't understand me like he does either way
Are you exercising for the upcoming sports festival?
Well more like I realized I'd be in trouble if I was out of shape in the zombie apocalypse happened. Yeah
Yeah
Not knowing when the world will come to an end only thing you can count on is yourself
true
Okay, well, then how about we race?
How far are we going?
Finish line
That's former sports club endurance for you. Oh, yeah, what?
So we have all the stuff in my house. Want a quickie?
What stuff a quickie?
My mom's away for work in Toyosu today. This is turning downright sinful
Ever seen one of these what could it be for that thing's an ab roller
Right and it actually works, too
Should have known she'd never do anything so improper
But I would hardly call this proper either
You really work out at home it seems, huh?
I never expected that of you
Every single girl in the world minds their weight
Get him out of the way
Go on! Scram! He's a lot heavier than he looks
Which one of you was it? Huh? It was what?
too long
Oh
This is harder than it looks
I mean, this is harder than it looks.
Goodness, these are my dads.
Wanna try them out?
You expect me to lift something even you can't?
But aren't you prepping for your one-on-one?
I never expected that of you.
Never saw someone get challenged like that in real life.
Why'd you take him up?
Because... Arachi's my friend.
He seems serious.
Mm-hmm.
Arachi likes Yamada.
Let's go one-on-one!
He probably sees what's going on between us.
Hey, Kyoro, do you like your eggs sweet?
Or do you like them more salty instead?
But I don't want to lose.
Because Yamada is who...
It's the sweeter buns...
Huh?
I like!
Careful!
Like the sweet sort that much?
Yeah.
Okay.
Don't bring a lunch for the sports festival then.
Huh?
I'm gonna work hard.
On what?
Cheese!
Feels good to be third years and get all done up without worrying what the older kids think anymore.
There we are!
Looks good!
Well...
What to write?
Your boo's name?
The Mokotanmen guy.
Who?
And just like that, the sports festival was here.
Boo!
What?
Stand still!
Tell me that's not permanent.
Hmm.
Hmmm.
Oh?
Now, don't let that come off.
Okay?
weather forecast says it'll rain this afternoon not that i care if this whole thing gets called
off in fact i'd be thrilled and now a pledge from one of our students
he practiced this speech so many times yesterday
he's serious about this we all pledge to work hard and fully throb with sportsmanship and play fairly and enthusiastically with all our members with all our members with all our members with all our members
i can't believe it he still forced that dick crap in
in here i thought he was serious i'm definitely not going down not to this guy
look here i made some fans they can't look this way though
oh you're right she's good with her hands but basically another yamada
scavenger hunt scavenger hunt
i gotta find a couple even a pair not going out yet will do
that's obviously her handwriting now where am i gonna find a pair of hot lost birds
yamada hey but i'm not you've got to look here fan
what no anyone else then
um
um well
we came in first
spooky put me down
i'm sorry was i not clear on how bad i want to win
knew that had to be a trap
uh
huh
he warming up
uh
cut it out right now yamada
this is no time to play around
you can do this yamada
yamada
wait
this guy
he never changes
but
that's what i like about him
you've done this before ichikawa
i remember you getting in my way once
we are now discussing how to proceed with the rest of the games
in light of the current weather conditions
please await further instructions
i would say this means no cavalry game in an early launch what do you think
guess we'll have to call it off
it's only just a drizzle though
we can handle a little rain
oh
it'll be all guys so no need to worry about wet shirt
that's not the issue
let's do it
uh
i'll get it done and make it quick
if anyone's gonna end this stupid thing
it's gonna be me
once we start rush straight ahead
just do it
all right i'll do it
ranger is coming down hard
can we please go inside now
am i doing this for adachi
or for this thing called friendship
that i've always despised
no
it's nothing as noble as that
i just i i like anayamada
i know it's not just that
despite it all i think you're a great guy
that's why
that's why i
don't give me that
don't go talking like you know me at all
because you don't
and don't go claiming you like yamada
without knowing a damn thing about her
no guy who let himself believe that chocolate with an odd shame nut from seki name meant something
gets the claim he likes yamada
i know i get it okay
you don't though
yamada
is so much more grown up than us
she's absolutely incredible
she follows her dreams and works harder than anyone
you can't come in here claiming to like her just because she's cute and prettier than anyone you've ever seen
because listen
i'm telling you
that's not what liking someone is about
i'm aware of that
i'm pretty sure
i've lost already anyway
so just
let me go down
shamefully in the way i deserve to
don't go accepting it
huh
are you kidding me
cut the crap
you still like your for all that right
you're serious about this aren't you
then tell me off
come on
show me you mean it
why what difference would it make
it makes no difference at all
the hell
but i mean it
i really do like
yamada
starting to get cold
wanna head under the tents
can't really hear them but sounds like they're fighting with one another huh
guess we can keep watching though
what do you want me to do then
i don't know
you're the one who wanted to go one on one
so come on then
damn it
why are you acting like this now
i didn't know you man
i could eventually
have learned to
hate her
die
and
you
And the rain washes it all away.
Ichikawa? There, there.
Go home already, Mom.
I'm a licensed nurse, okay?
Uh, later then.
What's this about?
This thing is practically soaked.
She's pretty cute.
Hey!
Um, are you Ichikawa's sister?
Huh?
Get lost, kid.
I lost.
Yeah.
But hey, one thing my mom always told me, is that not ever forgetting that disappointment
is the most important part of moving on when it comes to life lessons.
Disappointment.
That's what I've been hiding from all this time.
I'll leave this here for you.
For me?
Yep.
It's your lunch.
It's huge.
This is the one that came out best.
Right.
Also, here's some chicken karaage.
More like rice balls.
The chicken's inside.
And all of them?
Want to try some of the eggs?
Sure.
Careful.
I gotta keep a straight face.
If this tastes bad, it'll show and...
Yum.
Oh, I'm happy.
No, I really mean it's good.
Just right.
Not too sweet.
Perfectly cooked.
Oh, no, I wasn't asking for any.
I just wanted to see your face.
Want some?
But those snacks are all for you.
What do you think I am, Asuma?
A sumo?
What do you think I am, a sumo wrestler?
I'll go grab my lunch too then.
No, don't.
People will get the wrong idea.
You know...
Kyou?
You were really cool.
Yummy.